

[Johan Try Affandy, S.T.]

Magetan, East Java, 63319 | 081 3366 7676 1 | johan.tryaffandy@gmail.com
@jhon_affandy in johantryaffandy

About Me

My name is Johan Try Affandy, and I am 25 years old. I am a bachelor of Electrical Engineering freshgraduate at Sebelas Maret University of Surakarta especially in Electrical Power System. I have an internship experience at PT Telkom Indonesia Witel Yogyakarta in Access Optima & Construction Division. I am interested in electrical engineering position, like power plant, automation, telecommunication and computers.

Expertise

Microsoft Office

ETAP

HOMER

Isis Proteus

AutoCad

Packet Tracer

Arduino

Work Experience

PT. Telkom Indonesia (Witel Yogyakarta)

Access Optima & Construction Division (Internship Program on July - August 2018)

Surveying plan site, supervising and testing the project.

Sedekah Rombongan (Magetan, Jawa Timur)

Non-Governmental Organization Volunteer (May 2018 - May 2019)

• Ambulance driver.

Lab Assistance (Electrical Engineering, UNS)

Power Electronics (November 2018 - January 2019)

• Organizing the practical of power electronics, preparing tools and materials.

Organizational Experience

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Elektro UNS 2018

Head of Organizational Regeneration and Development Department

- Make sure all the projects can be carry on.
- Projects: Upgrading, student gathering night, new student welcome event.
- Delegating the project to all the staff and keep in touch on all the projects.

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Elektro UNS 2017

Staff of Organizational Regeneration and Development Department

Coordinator of new student welcome event 2017

Education

Sebelas Maret University of Surakarta (2015-2019)

Bachelor of Electrical Engineering - 3,41 GPA

- Head of Organizational Regeneration and Development Department 2018.
- Passed student creative project with tittle "Smart Landslide Detector" funded by DIKTI 2017.

SMAN 1 Magetan (2012-2015)

Science program

- Staff of sports division at SMAN 1 Magetan student organization 2013 and 2014.
- Coordinator of Smasa Cup Futsal tournament in Madiun region 2014.

Projects

- Single Phase Inverter Design with Power Monitoring using Arduino 2019
- Smart Landslide Detector 2018
- Doorlock with Passcode 2017
- Car Parking Sensors using ultrasonic module 2016